Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000; Series II
  - King County, Washington - Monroe to Earlmont, North Bothell to South Renton, 1952-04-21; A1-L1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-13
  - King County, Washington - Monroe to Earlmont, North Bothell to South Renton, 1952-04-21; A1-L2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
  - King County, Washington - Monroe to Earlmont, North Bothell to South Renton, 1952-04-21; A1-L3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-10
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Lochsloy to West of Lake Stevens, 1955-06-07; A-18-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 018)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-11
    Index in box 018
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Lochsloy to West of Lake Stevens, 1955-06-07; A-18-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 018)
  - Lewis County, Washington - Castle Rock to Evaline, 1948-06-18; TG 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-17
  - Lewis County, Washington - East Castle Rock to Evaline, 1948-06-18; TG 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 18-34
  - Lewis County, Washington - Evaline to Grand Mound, 1948-06-28; TG 1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 35-46
  - Lewis County, Washington - Cowlitz River to Evaline (West of Napavine), 1948-06-28; TG 2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
  - Lewis County, Washington - West Silver Lake to Evaline, 1948-06-28; TG 2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 18-25
  - Lewis County, Washington - Napavine to east Grand Mound, 1948-06-28; TG 2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 26-59
  - Lewis County, Washington - North Evaline to Centralia, 1948-06-28; TG 2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 60-70
  - Thurston County, Washington - Bucoda vicinity, 1953-08-14; BBH-1M; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 125, 126, 134
  - Thurston County, Washington - Tenino vicinity, 1953-08-14; BBH-1M; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 121, 136, 137
  - Thurston County, Washington - Bucoda vicinity, 1955-06-06; C-11; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-16 to 2-20; 3-20 to 3-33; 434 to 4-44
    Index in box 019, 1 of 2 photo index sheets
  - Thurston County, Washington - West Centralia to Bucoda, 1955-06-06; C-11-4; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-34 thru 4-44
  - Thurston County, Washington - West Tenino to Deschutes River, 1955-06-06; C-11-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-9
  - Thurston County, Washington - Tenino vicinity, 1955-06-06; C-11; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 to 1-9; 2-10 to 2-16; 3-25
    Index in box 019, 2 of 2 photo index sheets
  - Thurston County, Washington - South Bucoca to North Tenino, 1955-06-06; C-11-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-10 thru 2-20
  - Thurston County, Washington - Tenino to East Olympia, 1955-06-06; C-11-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Hycon Aerial Surveys (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-21 thru 3-33
  - Thurston County, Washington - Yelm and McKenna vicinity, 1954-05-16; BBH-3M; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 100, 101, 128, 129
  - Thurston County, Washington - Shelton to Tumwater vicinity, 1968-02-05; HC-17; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-2 thru 1-4, 1-8 thru 1-15
  - Thurston County, Washington - Olympia to Tumwater to Lacey, 1953-08-14; BBH-1M; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Commodity Stabilization Service (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 86-90, 108-111, 113
  - Thurston County, Washington - Tumwater to Olympia, 1951-08-18; D-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 01-07
  - Thurston County, Washington - Tumwater to Olympia, 1951-08-18; D-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 01-06
  - Thurston County, Washington - Olympia to Union Mills, 1955-10-13; C-12; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Scale: 1:10,000
  - Thurston County, Washington - Olympia to Tumwater to Lacey, 1952-06-08; G6, G7; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: G6 1-4; G7 1-4
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Tunnel Island to Pacific Beach, 1952-06-17; C-1-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Photographic Surveys (Western) Ltd. (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-14
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Moclips River to East Fork Hoquiam River, 1955-10-01; C-13-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pafford, Jones and White (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-11
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - South New London to East Fork Humptulips River, 1955-10-01; C-13-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pafford, Jones and White (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-1 thru 2-11
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Hoquiam to North New London, 1955-10-01; C-13-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pafford, Jones and White (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-8
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Hoquiam to Aberdeen, 1955-10-01; C20-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Pafford, Jones and White (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-3 thru 1-12
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Hoquiam to Aberdeen, 1955-10-01; C20-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-3 thru 2-16
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Hoquiam to Aberdeen, 1955-10-01; C20-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 019)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-14
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - West Satsop to Elma, 1956-06-28; C21-6; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 6-1 thru 6-7, 6-12
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - West Satsop to Elma, 1956-06-28; C21-5; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-1 thru 5-8, 5-13
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Central Park - Montesano - Melbourne area, 1956-06-28; C21-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-17
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Central Park - Montesano - Melbourne area, 1956-06-28; C21-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-4
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Central Park - Montesano - Melbourne area, 1956-06-28; C21-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-4 thru 2-12
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Central Park - Montesano - Melbourne area, 1956-06-28; C21-4; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-1 thru 4-3
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - South Montesano, Undated; C21-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-9 thru 3-14
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - South Montesano, 1956-06-28; C21-4; WA State Highway Commission (DOT) (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-9 thru 4-14
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington - Puget Island to Pacific County Line, 1952-04-04; D2-3; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Delano aerial Surveys (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-1 thru 3-16
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington - Skamokawa to East Cathlamet, 1952-04-04; D2-1; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Delano aerial Surveys (Box 020)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-20
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington - Puget Island to South Fork Grays River, 1952-04-04; D2-2; WA State Highway Commission (DOT); Delano aerial Surveys (Box 020)
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington - Aberdeen, Washington (other unidentified photos[SC-C-85]), 1965-1967 [1985]; + [SC-C-85] (Box-folder 021/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4 photos + [01-045-044]
  - Possibly Phillipines, Undated (Box-folder 021/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1 + photcopies
  - Korea, Undated (Box-folder 021/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 10 photos
  - Possibly Phillipines, Japan, Korea, Palau, Undated (Box-folder 021/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 27 photos (plus 3 photocopies)
  - Skagit County, Washington - South Cascade Glacier, 1980-10-03 (Box-folder 021/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-8 thru 3-10
  - Information, correspondence re: Canada-Alaska Highway, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 021/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 6 photos
    Includes Archie Shiels' correspondence.
  - Aleutian Islands: Onnekotan, Kiska, Adak, Kaganul, Undated (Box-folder 021/07)
  - Alaska, General - Glaciers: Eagle, Malaspina, Muldrow, Ellsworth, Twin, Taku, Davidson, Excelsior, circa 1946-1951 (Box-folder 021/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 11 photos
  - Alaska, Anchorage Area - South, West, circa 1950 (Box-folder 021/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5 photos
  - Alaska - Brooks Range - North Slope and South of Brooks Range, circa 1950 (Box-folder 021/10)
  - Alaska - Fairbanks Area - Northeast of Fairbanks, circa 1950 (Box-folder 021/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1 photo
  - Alaska - Juneau Area - Iliamna Volcano, circa 1950 (Box-folder 021/12)
  - Alaska - Mt. Katmai Area, circa 1950 (Box-folder 021/13)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2 photos
  - Alaska - Mt. McKinley Area (8 photos Muldrow Glacier), circa 1950 (Box-folder 021/14)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 13 photos
  - Alaska - Northern, 1948-1949; BAR (Box-folder 021/15)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 41 photos
  - Alaska - Norton Sound, Undated (Box-folder 021/16)
  - Alaska - Southeast, 1948; SEA-65; SEA-95; SEA-138 (Box-folder 021/17)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12 photos
  - Alaska - Tanana (Junction of Yukon and Tanana Rivers, Undated (Box-folder 021/18)
  - Alaska - Yakutat Bay, 1959 (two photos) (Box-folder 021/19)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4 photos
  - Alaska - Yukon Delta, Undated (Box-folder 021/20)
  - B.C. - Alaska Highway, Undated (Box-folder 021/21)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 160 photos (approx.)
  - Notes, maps, correspondence, 2000-09-18 (Box-folder 021/22)
  - Colville National Forest, Washington, 7/24/1986 and 10/15/1986; BPA-BD1 (Box-folder 022/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1A-1 thru 20A-9
  - Cape Flattery, Washington, 1974-09-21; MLM-74 (Box-folder 022/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 4-9
    Scale: 1:17,000
    Index filed with photographs.
  - Steamboat Mountain Project, 9/3/1963 and 9/18/1963; GS-VATK (Box-folder 022/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-117
  - Spokane and Pend Oreille County, Washington, 1974 and 1975; POS-C-74 (Box-folder 022/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 36 photos
  - Okanogan County, Washington, 1983-08-04; CIRW (Box-folder 022/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1-3 thru 1-5-129
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington, 1979; OC-C-79 (Box-folder 023/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Uncounted
  - Unidentified, 1965-09-07; WFOA-65 (Box-folder 023/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 39-36
  - Mt. Baker to Snohomish County, Washington, circa 1946; H. D48 (Box-folder 023/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-4 thru 1-15; 2-37 thru 2-48
  - Chelan National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-18; GS-QD (Box-folder 023/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-5, 6, 44, 45, 63, 64, 113, 114, 122, 123
  - Glacier Peak?, 1950-08-17; GS-LL (Box-folder 023/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Various
  - Control photostats GS-CJ, 1947-08-26; GS-CJ (Box-folder 023/06)
  - Unidentified, Undated; 33-2-371 (Box-folder 024/01)
  - Snoqualmie-White River, Washington, 1951-07-27; P.A.S. (Box-folder 024/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-11 (two sets)
  - Snohomish County, Washington - (neArizonaKing County Line) South to North, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-56-97 thru 1-56-155
  - Snohomish County, Washington - East of Lake Stevens/Machias area South to North, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-57-165 thru 1-57-182
  - Snohomish County, Washington - From King County line north to Monroe, Washington, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-57-273 thru 1-57-283
  - Snohomish County, Washington - From King County line north of Bothell to east of Everett, Washington, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-50-213 thru 2-50-240
  - Snohomish County, Washington - King County Line west of Echo Lake north to Arlington Heights, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-55-87 thru 2-55-142
  - Snohomish County, Washington - King County Line south of Edmonds, Washington to Edmonds, Washington, 1995-04-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-40-127 thru 3-40-132
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Edmonds, Washington, 1995-04-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-41-256 thru 3-41-262
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Brier, Washington area to Possession Sound, Washington, 1995-04-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/10)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-45-54 thru 3-45-78
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Esperance, Washington to Picnic Point Beach, 1995-04-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-42-119 thru 4-42-129
  - Snohomish County, Washington - King County Line/Lake Ballinger to Mukilteo, 1995-04-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/12)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-43-251 thru 4-43-270
  - Snohomish County, Washington - King County Line/Lake Pleasant to South Everett, Washington, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/13)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-48-205 thru 5-48-231
  - Snohomish County, Washington - King County Line at I-405 to Everett, Washington, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/14)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-49-86 thru 5-49-112
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Stickney Lake, Washington to east of Mukilteo, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/15)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4-46-121 thru 4-46-126, 129-132
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Alderwood Manor, Washington area to, 1995-04-24; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/16)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 6-47-90 thru 6-47-113
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Mountlake Terrace, Washington to Mukilteo, Washington, 1995-04-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/17)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 7-44-130 thru 7-44-151
  - Snohomish County, Washington - North of Woodinville, Washington to north of Arlington, Washington near Skagit County border, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 024/18)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 9-51-84 thru 9-51-137
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Maltby, Washington to north of Arlington, Washington near Skagit County border, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 11-53-279 thru 11-53-334
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Crystal Lake, Washington to north of Arlington Heights, Washington, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 11-54-142 thru 11-54-197
  - Snohomish County, Washington - west of Marysville, Washington to Skagit County border south of Lake McMurray, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-48-218 thru 12-48-244
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Everett, Washington to Skagit County border southeast of Lake McMurray, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-49-175 thru 12-49-209
  - Snohomish County, Washington - east of Everett (Spencer Island) to Skagit County border southeast of Lake McMurray, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-50-139 thru 12-50-172
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Maltby, Washington to north of Arlington, Washington near Skagit County border, 1995-05-19; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-52-83 thru 12-52-138
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Monroe, Washington to east of Lake Stevens, 1995-05-21; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 17-57-2 thru 17-57-20
  - Snohomish County, Washington - south of Monroe, Washington to north of Granite Falls, Washington, 1995-05-21; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 17-58-105 thru 17-58-146
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Brier, Washington to Paine Field, 1995-05-25; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 18-46-324 thru 18-46-338
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Gedney Island, Washington, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/10)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-43-146 thru 19-43-150
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Northwest of Tulalip, Washington to Lake Ketchum area near Skagit County border, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-43-152 thru 19-43-176
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Tulalip Bay, Washington to Skagit County border at I-5, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/12)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-44-108 thru 19-44-136
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Gedney Island, Washington, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/13)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-44-142 thru 19-44-145
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Tulalip Bay, Washington to Skagit County border east of I-5, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 025/14)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-45-73 thru 19-45-102
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Priest Point/Tulalip area to Skagit County border southeast of Lake McMurray, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 026/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-46-38 thru 19-46-69
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Port Gardner/Possession Sound to Skagit County border southwest of Lake McMurray, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 026/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19-47-1 thru 19-47-34
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Mouth of Stillaguamish River to Skagit County line northwest of Lake Ketchum, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 026/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 20-40-161 thru 20-40-173
  - Snohomish County, Washington - South of Kayak Point to west of Lake Ketchum, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 026/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 20-41-101 thru 20-41-124
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Tulalip Bay to Lake Ketchum, 1995-05-23; NW-95 (Box-folder 026/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 20-42-1 thru 20-42-30
  - Snohomish County, Washington - Everett/Port Gardner to south of Lake McMurray, 1995-05-26; NW-95 (Box-folder 026/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 27-48-9 thru 27-48-18, 20-22
  - Chelan, County, Washington, 1976-09-20; PR1 (Box-folder 026/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PR1 2 thru 19
  - Chelan, County, Washington, 1976-09-20; PR2 (Box-folder 026/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PR2 2 thru 15
  - Chelan, County, Washington, 1976-09-20; PR3 (Box-folder 026/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PR3 4 thru 14
  - Chelan, County, Washington, 1976-09-21; PR8, PR10, PR11, PR11A, PR12A (Box-folder 026/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: PR8-5and6; PR10-2; PR11 2,3,4; PR11A 2,3,4; PR12A-9
  - Port Angeles, Washington, 1939-08-01; GS-J (Box-folder 026/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-81 thru 5-83; 6-64 thru 6-65
  - Port Angeles, Washington, 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 026/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 172 31
  - Port Angeles, Washington, 1980-07-07; 626090 (Box-folder 026/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 279-16 and 279-17
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1964-05-15; OLY 64 (Box-folder 026/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-21 thru 5-23; 6-25 thru 6-31; 7B-20 thru 7B-29; 8-28 thru 8-37; 9A-34 thru 9A-40; 10-37 thru 10-40; 11-40
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1965-06-07; OLY 65 (Box-folder 026/10)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46A-35 thru 46A-48; 47-43 thru 47-50
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1981-07-26; OL 81 (Box-folder 026/11)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1990-07-11; OL 90 (Box-folder 026/12)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1997-08-01; OL 97 (Box-folder 026/13)
  - Yakima area, Washington, 1949-06-30; NL (Box-folder 027/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NL-5F-27
  - Yakima area, Washington, 1949-06-30; NL (Box-folder 027/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: NL-5F-28; NL-5F-29
  - Squalicum Harbor, Bellingham, Washington, circa 1971 (Box-folder 027/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 31 copies
  - Bellingham, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 027/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-1GG-9 (17 copies)
  - Bellingham, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 027/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-1GG-10 (17 copies)
  - Bellingham, Washington (north), 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 027/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-1GG-31 and 32
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 027/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-1GG-80 and 81
  - Nooksack, Washington, 1970-06-02; NW-69 (Box-folder 027/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 235 44B-102 (19 copies) and Similar flight line (17 copies)
  - Bellingham, Washington, 1947-07-20; BBK-3B (Box-folder 027/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-3B-112 (34 copies)
  - Bellingham, Washington, 1947-07-20; BBK-3B (Box-folder 027/10)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-3B-113 and 114
  - Sehome Hill area, Bellingham, Washington, circa 1970 (Box-folder 027/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19 copies
  - Bellingham, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 027/12)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 43-36C-20 (20 copies) and 43-36C-21 (17 copies)
  - Bellingham, Washington (I-5 at Meridian), 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 027/13)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 43-36C-22 and 43-36C-23
  - Unidentified, 1983-07-29; NW-C-83 (Box-folder 027/14)
  - Whatcom County, Washington (Acme and Bellingham), 1955-08-06; BBK-3P (Box-folder 027/15)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BBK-3P-84 and BBK-3P-119
  - Cascade Mountains, Washington, 1955-07-20; GS-VJQ (Box-folder 028/01)
  - Province of British Columbia, Canada, 1993-1994; BCC93039; BCC93041; BCC94044; BCC94088 (Box-folder 028/02)
  - Province of British Columbia, Canada, 1995-05-14; SRS 5458; Triathlon Mapping Corp and Selkirk Remote Sensing, Ltd. (Box-folder 028/03)
  - Province of British Columbia, Canada, 1999-05-22; SRS 6064; Selkirk Remote Sensing, Ltd. (Box-folder 028/04)
  - Unidentified, 05-12-1983; 05-19-1983; 0-83-ARC; Bureau of Land Management (Box-folder 028/05)
  - Spokane County, Washington, 1957-06-30; AAN (Box 029)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 15T; 16T
  - Spokane County, Washington, 1957-07-10; AAN (Box 030)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 17T; 18T
  - Spokane County, Washington, 1957-07-10; AAN (Box 031)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 18T; 19T
  - Spokane County, Washington, 1957-07-24; AAN (Box 032)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 19T; 20T
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1957-07-24; BBD (Box 033)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 22T; 23T
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1957-08-16; BBD (Box 034)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 26T; 27T
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1957-06-17; BBD (Box 035)